Contact

bdcorb@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/barrydavidcorb-msn-hcsm-rn-ccrncmc-01aa7099 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Critical Care Hospitals

Certifications

CCRN (Critical Care Certified)-AACN
CMC (Cardiac Medicine Certified)AACN

Honors-Awards

FMOLHS Leadership MOST TEAM SPIRIT AWARD

GREAT 100 NURSE HONOR RECIPIENT

Nurse Excellence Award "BEST NURSE IN A CRISIS"

Nurse Excellence Award "BEST CHARGE NURSE"

EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH

BarryDavid Corb, MSN-HCSM, RN, CCRN-CMC

Chief Clinical Officer at BridgePoint Continuing Care Hospital Greater New Orleans Area

Summary

BarryDavid Corb, MSN-HCSM, RN, CCRN-CMC is the Chief Clinical Officer for BridgePoint Continuing Care Hospital. Mr. Corb earned his MSN with an emphasis on Health Care Systems Management from Loyola University in New Orleans, Louisiana. With 19 years of experience, Mr. Corb has fulfilled roles that range from direct patient care and management of multiple hospital units and product lines to senior leadership. As a Certified Critical Care & Cardiac Medicine nurse and an expert in critical and intensive care, he has achieved high level improvements through his leadership in patient safety and nursing efficiency, working diligently to ensure both staff and facility operate at a superior level using evidence-based best practices, optimizing the patient experience and driving quality outcomes.

Experience

BridgePoint Healthcare Chief Clinical Officer September 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Perfusion Vascular Labs

Greater New Orleans Area

Vice President of Vascular Services for Perfusion Vascular Labs February 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 8 months)

Hammond, Louisiana

MedCentris

Director of Operations

May 2016 - September 2018 (2 years 5 months)

Hammond, Louisiana

Comprehensive Wound Medicine & Limb Salvage Services

Baton Rouge General Medical Center

House Supervisor February 2016 - July 2016 (6 months)

Baton Rouge, Louisiana Area

Nursing Administration

St. Elizabeth Hospital
Divisional Director of Nursing
October 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 4 months)
Gonzales, Louisiana

West Jefferson Medical Center Clinical Director of Critical Care (ICU/CCU/SCU) June 1999 - September 2014 (15 years 4 months)

Education

Loyola University New Orleans

MSN-HCSM, Health Care Systems Management/Nursing

Administration · (2013 - 2015)

Our Lady of Holy Cross College BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse